<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Compass CBT</title>
    <link>https://compasscbt.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Compass CBT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 16:06:27 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://compasscbt.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://compasscbt.com/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 16:06:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://compasscbt.com/resources/</guid>
      <description>Meditations The following are guided meditations, narrated by me. May they be of benefit to you.
Brief Self-Compassion: this short meditation is intended to instill a sense of self-compassion by relating to yourself as you would to a good friend. This meditation is adapted from the work of Kristen Neff, PhD.
Soften, Soothe, Allow: this is a meditation for dealing with difficult emotions.This meditation is adapted from the work of Kristen Neff, PhD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Areas of Expertise</title>
      <link>https://compasscbt.com/expertise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 17:34:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://compasscbt.com/expertise/</guid>
      <description>While some people seek treatment for specific mental health conditions, it is not necessary to know or even meet criteria for a mental health diagnosis in order to benefit from therapy. I recognize that therapy is a very personal process and you are a complex human being. While I have the expertise to assess symptoms and provide appropriate diagnoses, I also go above and beyond to treat each client as an individual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Dr. Lazarovich</title>
      <link>https://compasscbt.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 20:01:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://compasscbt.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Regina Lazarovich, Ph.D.  Licensed Clinical Psychologist in California (PSY&amp;hellip;) and New York (020676)
  I know that entering therapy can feel scary and vulnerable. I founded Compass CBT with the intention of providing a safe and non-judgmental space for the life-changing work of therapy. I approach each client with warmth, curiosity and respect. While some people know what they want from therapy, not everyone does, and that’s okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treatment Approaches</title>
      <link>https://compasscbt.com/approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 20:01:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://compasscbt.com/approach/</guid>
      <description>I have extensive training and expertise in a variety of evidence-based therapeutic approaches. When creating a treatment plan, I will draw from the approaches that are most relevant to your circumstances and needs. My expertise includes, but is not limited to:
Cognitive Behavioral Therapy (CBT) CBT is a therapeutic approach that focuses on changing patterns of thinking and behavior associated with distress. CBT consists of:
 Cognitive therapy strategies focused on identifying and changing thought patterns that are causing and maintaining problematic emotions and behaviors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://compasscbt.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 23:21:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://compasscbt.com/</guid>
      <description>I am Dr. Regina Lazarovich, Ph.D., clinical psychologist and founder of Compass CBT. My mission is to help you find the life you want. I provide evidence-based cognitive behavior therapy with a compassionate individually-tailored approach. Together we can identify and change unhelpful patterns of thought and behavior that cloud your path. It is never too late to improve your quality of life and experience profound personal growth.
&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://compasscbt.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 22:01:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://compasscbt.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>      Contact Us   Stop by for a visit  123 Office Park Road, Scotts Valley, CA   hello@compasscbt.com   &amp;#43;1 347-735-9740   {{ range .Site.Params.contact.social }}    {{ end }}  --     </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>